Pause slideshow Play slideshow

[**TODAY ONLY:** Free FULL-SIZE TriHydrate Hyaluronic Acid Serum with Purchases $75+](https://www.serovital.com/collections/all-products "All Products")

SeroVital [ ](https://www.serovital.com/)[ ](https://www.serovital.com/)

[Search](https://www.serovital.com/search) [Account](https://www.serovital.com/account) [0 Cart](https://www.serovital.com/cart) ... Site navigation

Close

   Search Close

Cancel

Subtotal

$0.00

CHECK OUT

Shipping, taxes, and discount codes calculated at checkout.

Your cart is currently empty.

* 
    
    SHOP Expand submenu
    * SHOP

View more

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

#### Unsolicited Email (SPAM)

Your privacy is very important to us. Be assured that, in accordance with this privacy policy, we do not sell or distribute our customer list to third parties. You should be aware, however, that unscrupulous marketers can sometimes "harvest" your email address directly from your computer or another person's address book or even obtain your email address through programs that automatically search web pages and email traffic for email addresses.

Please note that all email that originates from us will either display the company logo (HTML emails) or contain any company copyright notice (text emails). In addition, our emails will contain the address of origination. We also provide you with an opt-out method on any email you receive from us (aside from order confirmation and tracking emails). If you receive an unsolicited email that you believe originates from our company, please forward us the email so we may investigate the matter further.

#### Your Consent

By entering personally identifiable information on any of our Web sites, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time. If we ever change our privacy policy, we will post any changes online or send you an email so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Unless we clearly state otherwise, the changes to our privacy policy will affect only the information we collect after the effective date of the change.

#### Collection and Use of Information

Information Collection: We endeavor to strictly adhere to state, local and federal laws regarding the preservation and archiving of information collected. We collect information from you in several different ways on our Site. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:

* help make our Site easier for you to use by removing the need to enter information more than once.
    
* help you quickly find information, products, and services.
    
* help us create content on our Site that is most relevant to you.
    
* alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.

1. Registration and Ordering: Before using certain parts of our Site or ordering products, you must complete an online registration form. During registration, you will be prompted to provide to us certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, shipping and billing address(es), phone number, email address, and credit card number. These kinds of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and our Site, and for marketing purposes. Also, if we encounter a problem when processing your order, we use the personal information to contact you.
2. Email Addresses: Several locations of our Site permit you to enter your email address for purposes including but not limited to: to sign up for our email newsletter, to submit a product review, to post comments in our forums, to register for a free giveaway or other promotional offer and to request notifications of new product offerings.
3. Cookies and Other Technology: Like many sites, our Site employs cookies, JavaScript tags and Web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or "action tags") to speed your navigation of our Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your usage of our Site.

* Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from Web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of our Site.
* We use both persistent cookies and third party cookies. We use persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. The persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Third party cookies are only used for short-term tracking. You can remove the cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent and third party cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some areas of our Site, such as a shopping cart, will be limited and may not function properly.
* OUR SITE'S COOKIES DO NOT AND CANNOT INFILTRATE A USER'S HARD DRIVE TO GATHER A USER'S CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION. Our cookies are not spyware.
* Web beacons assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a Web page on our Site has been viewed and, if so, how many times. For example, any electronic image on our Site, such as an ad banner, can function as a Web beacon.
* We may use third-party advertising companies to help us tailor our Site's content to users or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and Web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness (such as which Web pages are visited or what products are purchased and in what amount). Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and Web beacons is not linked to you directly.
* As an example, Facebook collects certain information via cookies and Web beacons to determine which Web pages are visited or what products are purchased. Please note that any information collected by Facebook via cookies and Web beacons is not linked to any customer's personal information collected by us.
* SeroVital.com uses cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping cart including when you have abandoned your cart and, if you opt into receive SMS marketing messages from us, this information is used to determine when to send cart reminder messages via SMS.
* Sharing of personal information for targeted advertising based on your interaction on different websites may be considered “sales,” “sharing,” or “targeted advertising under certain U.S. state privacy laws. Depending on where you live, you may have the right to opt out of these activities. If you would like to opt out of these activities, please see information about how to opt out, below.
* Third-party vendors may pool the anonymous information that they collect from our website with other sources of information, which may include your name and mailing address, for purposes of determining whether you might be interested in receiving direct mail. If you do not wish for cookies to be placed on your computer, most web browsers permit you to prevent that from taking place. Additionally, information about opting out of cookie-based Internet advertising can be found via the following links - [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/) and/or [https://www.neustar.biz/privacy/opt-out](https://www.neustar.biz/privacy/opt-out). However, please keep in mind that these technologies are an important part of how the website works; removing, rejecting or limiting the use of cookies or other similar technologies might affect the availability and functionality of the website. To opt-out of receiving our direct mail, you may send us an email at [customerservice@serovital.com](mailto:customerservice@serovital.com) or call us at [1-800-435-1409](tel:18004351409).

5. Log Files: As is true of most Web sites, our Site's servers automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access our Site as well as the site that you came from. We may also log your Internet protocol ("IP") address, Internet service provider, browser type, operating system and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing, and system troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address indicates your internet service provider)
6. Age: We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. Elsewhere on our Site, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or using the Site with the supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.
7. Product Reviews: You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, you have the option to enter your name and email address. If you submit a review, your name or alias will be visible to other users but your email address will be kept private. Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to our Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing any personal information. Your review or comment might be altered or deleted if inappropriate words or terms have been used. You may withdraw your review at any time by contacting our Customer Service department. Contact information for Customer Service can be found on the Contact Us page of our Site.
8. External Reviews: We use a series of external review services such as Bazaarvoice to permit shoppers to rate their experiences while visiting and shopping at our Sites. After placing an order at our Site, you may receive the opportunity to provide feedback on your experience. This choice is optional and will not affect your order or service from our Site, whether or not you choose to provide feedback. Your feedback is collected by the external service, not us, and is governed by their privacy policies. Contact the respective review service to view their privacy policies. For example, the Bazaarvoice privacy policy is available at [https://www.bazaarvoice.com/legal/privacy-policy/](https://www.bazaarvoice.com/legal/privacy-policy/)

#### Information Use and Disclosure

1. Internal Use: We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve our Site's content and layout, to improve our outreach and for marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to our Site.
2. Communications with You: We will use your personal information to communicate with you about our Site and your orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. We may send you a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary (for example, if we must temporarily suspend our service for maintenance.) Also, you may submit your email address for reasons such as to receive our email newsletter, to receive information from our community forums, to register for a free giveaway or other promotional offer and to request notifications of new product offerings. If you submit your email address, we use it to deliver information to you. We always permit you to unsubscribe or opt out of future emails (see the opt out section, below, for more details). Because we have to communicate with you about orders that you choose to place, you cannot opt out of receiving emails related to your orders. We might also send you marketing material by means of standard mail such as offers, promotions, postcards or catalogs (see the opt out section below for removal options).

#### California Residents - California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)

1. We do not sell your personal information to any third party. We use it solely as set forth herein. If you are a California resident, the CCPA grants you certain rights, including the right to request access to the personal information we collect and use, the right to request deletion of certain personal information we have collected, and the right not to be discriminated against for having exercised your rights under the CCPA.
2. You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see details below), we will disclose to you: (1) the categories of personal information we collected about you; (2) the categories of courses for the personal information we collected about you; (3) our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information; (4) the categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information; (5) the specific pieces of personal information we collected about you; and (6) if we disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, the personal information categories that each category or recipient obtained.
3. During the last 12 months, we have collected the following categories of personal information about consumers (for a full description of these categories, see Collection and Use of Information above) from the listed categories of sources, and have shared the information with the following categories of third parties:  
    
    | Categories of personal information collected: | Collected from the following categories of sources: | Categories of third parties with which the category of information has been shared: |
    | --- | --- | --- |
    | Information you provide when you register and order with us: your name, billing and shipping address, phone number, email address, and credit card number. | From the consumer directly. | Credit card processors, data processing companies, email service providers, and media buyers. |
    | Email addresses. | From the consumer directly. | Credit card processors, data processing companies, email service providers, and media buyers. |
    | Cookies and other technology (JavaScript tags and Web beacons). | From the consumer visiting the site. | Credit card processors, data processing companies, email service providers, and media buyers. |
    | Log files. | From the consumer visiting the site. | Credit card processors, data processing companies, email service providers, and media buyers. |
    | Age of consumer. | From the consumer directly. | Credit card processors, data processing companies, email service providers, and media buyers. |
    | Product reviews. | From the consumer directly. | These are stored with a third party data processor, which helps facilitate the review process, and shared with third party retailers for their product reviews. |
    | External reviews. | From consumer directly via third party websites. | These are stored on third party retailers’ websites. We have no control over this data. |
    
4. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not deny you goods or services, charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, provide you a different level or quality of goods or services, or suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services. However, we may offer you certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA that can result in different prices, rates, or quality levels. Any CCPA-permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal information’s value and contain written terms that describe the program’s material aspects. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt-in consent, which you may revoke at any time.
5. If you are a California resident and wish to exercise any of these rights, either (1) send a verifiable consumer request by emailing us at customerservice@serovital.com, or (2) call the following toll-free telephone number: (800)898-5153. Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child. You may only make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information twice within a 12-month period. Your verifiable consumer request must (1) provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative, and (2) describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us. However, we do consider requests made through your password protected account sufficiently verified when the request relates to personal information associated with that specific account.

STAY CONNECTED

 Enter your email  

SUBSCRIBE

SeroVital

Policies

Get in touch

Follow us

\*These statements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.

^Cannot be combined with other offers or applied to past purchases; Cyber Monday offers (30% Off and Free Gift with $75 minimum purchase) exclude Holiday Kits and select bundle products. For new subscription sign-ups, additional 30% savings applies only to your first shipment; after your first order, regular subscription savings will apply. Offer ends 12/3/24 at 11:59pm PST.

SeroVital is protected by U.S. Patent Numbers 8,551,542; 8,715,752; 8,722,114; 8,734,864; 8,747,921; 8,747,922; 8,765,195; 8,808,763; 8,808,764; 8,815,311; 9,066,953; 9,198,889; 9,238,023; 9,339,490; and Canadian Patent Number: 2840809.  
The Smart Release compound in SeroVital Advanced is protected by U.S. Patent Number 9,114,091.

Free standard shipping on all U.S. orders.

**\*\*SeroVital has been shown in a double-blind, placebo-controlled clinical trial to increase mean, serum (blood) growth hormone levels by 682%.** All other benefits/effects noted in these testimonials/reviews are the individuals' personal opinions and have not been studied in relation to the SeroVital compound.  
⩔Individuals may have received free product or compensation in exchange for their honest review. Individual results will vary.

All trademarks are the property of their respective owners. © SanMedica (2012-2024) All Rights Reserved.

"Close (esc)"
